Elon Musk declares DEI must die as Tesla owner calls to end diversity, equity, and inclusion
initiatives. Can we let this man go, please? Can y'all let the Tesla go? Please, please. Now,
aside from the fact that he's just consistently saying racist, classist things, he is a problematic
person for a myriad of reasons. And here we have another one. Okay. This is the same person that
allowed for the controls on Twitter to be removed so that people would be free to say hateful,
hurtful things to you. Like that is a real thing. And that should not have been looked over. But
some of y'all really did because you're like, Oh, he makes money. I don't know what the obsession is
with these people who make money. The reality is that a lot of them are able to make money because
they had money. His father is a billionaire because of mines in Zambia that he tries to act like never
existed. But the dad is like, of course they existed. Yes. He is another one who raped Africa
and made the money off of it. So can you please let this man, his Tesla go? If you already got one,
I get it. But if you want one, let it go. To add to that, this man went to Israel a few weeks ago,
did not pay any attention to the Palestinians, knows that they do not have consistent internet.
Why? Because Israel controls it, which by the way, should tell you everything you need to know about
the dynamics of the situation. Because he is a bleeding heart capitalist, instead of providing
the internet service to the people who actually need it, he instead made a deal with a genocidal
maniac, Netanyahu, and said that they will be working together in the future. So that's who this person is.
Let him go!